https://www.sqlservercentral.com/privacy

Privacy Policy Redgate (which means Red Gate Software Limited and its subsidiary Red Gate Software Inc.) respects your privacy. All information you give us is held with the utmost care and security.
Please take time to review this privacy policy as it sets out our privacy practices and tells you how your personal information will be treated by us. We do not sell, rent or loan any identifiable information regarding our customers to any third party. Only in the circumstances described within this Privacy Policy would we share your information with any third party.
Our use of personal data is in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulations 2016 (GDPR).
How we use your information
Redgate is committed to protecting your privacy. If you're visiting our websites, using our products and services, working with any of our teams, meeting us at events or applying for a role with us, this privacy policy sets out what data we collect, and how we use it. It also describes your rights regarding our use of your data.
We collect common types of personal information, such as: name, job title, company, postal address, email address, phone number, and IP address.
We will use the personal information provided to us to:
Process orders submitted by you
Identify the Redgate 'certified partner' that is best placed to support your software purchase if you cannot purchase directly from us
Customize the service we provide to you
Administrate or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us
Verify your identity (e.g. if you participate in any promotions administered by us)
Anticipate and resolve any problems with any goods or services supplied to you
Carry out market research and surveys
Send you our newsletter, where this is requested by you
Track your engagement with us, including through our website, articles and newsletters
Understand how you use our products and services
Contact you by telephone and send you follow-up communications relating to your use of software downloaded from our website
Send you information about our other products and services
Process your application if you apply for a role with us
This privacy notice tells you what to expect when Redgate collects personal information. It contains more information about:
Visiting our websites
How we use cookies
Newsletters
Contacting us via social media
Contacting our product and support teams
Call recording
Information sent to us when you use our products
Applying for a role with us
Sharing your information with third parties
Transferring your information outside of the European Economic Area
Your rights
Complaints or queries
Reporting security issues
Changes to this privacy policy
Questions about data privacy
Visiting our websites
We also use third-party services to help us identify visitors to our website to improve the way we offer our products and services.
When you visit one of our websites, we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns, including through the use of third-party analytics services (such as Google Analytics). We do this to understand how people are using our websites, to manage their operation and to diagnose any problems.
Our website search is powered by Google. Search queries and results are logged anonymously to help us improve our website and search functionality. No user-specific data is collected by either Redgate or any third party.
How we use cookies
Your web browser allows you to control whether cookies can be stored by our websites. However, disabling cookies will prevent certain parts of our websites from working correctly. Your web browser’s documentation has more information on controlling cookie behaviour.
We use cookies on our websites to:
Maintain your active session
Store your preferences
Track the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns
Analyze the way people use our websites
Gather data on how our websites are performing
Newsletters
We send newsletters using HubSpot and Amazon Simple Email Service. We gather statistics around email opening and interaction using industry-standard technologies, including tracking pixels, to analyze the performance or email campaigns. We use data about your interactions with our emails as an indicator of your interest in our products. We may also use your interaction with our previous newsletters to send you more appropriate information in the future.
You can opt out of receiving these newsletters at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in these emails, or by managing your email preferences. For SQLServerCentral, manage your preferences on your profile page (linked from the top menu when logged in).
Contacting us via social media
Redgate maintains a presence on Twitter, Facebook and LinkedIn. We manage your interactions with us using HubSpot as well as using social media platforms directly.
If you send us a message via social media, we may include this in our CRM systems.
Contacting our product and support teams
If you engage with our support teams, we may ask you to provide additional information to help us assist you (like diagnostic logs). We may share this with our product development teams to enable them to reproduce and fix product issues.
Some of our products also include feedback mechanisms such as live chat. If you’re signed into the product, we’ll see your name and email address when you chat to us. Any information you send to us in the chat session will be shared with our product development and support teams.
Call recording
We record some calls for training and quality purposes to help us evaluate our performance and better understand the needs of our customers. If you live in the USA and two-party consent is required, we’ll let you know we’re recording the call at the start.
Information sent to us when you use our products
Our products send usage and fault reporting information to us. We use this to:
Measure how many people are using the different versions of our products, and the different features within them
Understand the environments in which our products are used (for example, the operating system version, SQL Server version, the amount of system memory and screen resolutions)
Measure the success of our sales and marketing operations
Guide product development decisions and improve our products
Assist you in your evaluation, purchasing, and renewal of our products
Some of our products allow you to submit error reports if something goes wrong. These contain logs and other diagnostic data, and you can choose to include your contact details and any additional information you think may be useful. Our support and development teams use this data to improve our products.
We use your basic environment and high-level usage data in conjunction with your records in our marketing and CRM systems. Your use of individual features is submitted anonymously and is not linked to your identity.
If you choose not to include diagnostic data with an error report, an anonymous record of the type of error which occurred will be sent. This allows us to measure how many of our customers experience errors and prioritise our focus for product development.
Applying for a role with us
If you apply for a role at Redgate, we will use the information you provide to assess your application.
If you are unsuccessful in your application, we will remove your data after 6 months. We may ask your permission to keep your details on file in our talent pool.
We use a third party, ICIMS, to manage our recruitment process. Their privacy policy is available here.
Sharing your information with third parties
Redgate uses select third parties to help us process data which helps us deliver our products and services to you. We do not sell any data regarding your use of our products or services except as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of Redgate, and we will ensure that your privacy continues to be protected.
Transferring your information outside of the European Economic Area
We may transfer your information to Red Gate Software Inc. and our service providers situated outside the European Economic Area [EEA], and it may be processed by staff operating outside the EEA. If we do this, we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected in accordance with EU data protection law.
Your rights
Under the GDPR, you have rights as an individual which you can exercise in relation to the information we hold about you:
Confirmation of personal data that is being processed
Access to your personal data
Other supplementary information as referred to (the information provided in our privacy policy)
Complaints and Queries
Redgate tries to meet the highest standards when collecting and using personal information. We take complaints very seriously. If you feel our collection or use of information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate, we encourage you to bring this to our attention. We also welcome any suggestions for improving our procedures.
If you have any questions regarding this policy, or wish to make a complaint about the way we’ve handled your personal information, contact privacy@red-gate.com.
Reporting Security Issues
If you become aware of a security vulnerability in any of Redgate's products, services or websites, contact security@red-gate.com.
We encourage the responsible disclosure of security issues, and will act quickly on any vulnerabilities reported. We will not take legal action against you if you:
Provide us with the information needed to reproduce and validate the vulnerability
Avoid violating the privacy of our customers, staff and other users
Avoid the destruction of data, or degradation of our services
Do not modify or access data that is not your own
Give us a reasonable time to address the issue before making any information public
Changes to this privacy policy
We regularly review our privacy policy. This policy was last updated on 16th May 2018.
Questions about data privacy
Redgate is the data controller for the information you provide unless otherwise stated. If you have any queries about the process or how we handle your information, contact privacy@red-gate.com.
You can also write to us at:
Data Protection Officer
Red Gate Software Limited
Newnham House
Cambridge Business Park
Cambridge
CB4 0WZ
SSC NewslettersSubscribe to the daily newsletter to get fresh SQL Server articles, scripts and info every day, and Database Weekly for a roundup of all the big stories in the SQL Server world.
Email
